♪ We ♪
♪ Are the crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And pearl ♪
And Steven!
红宝石们?
The Rubies?
哈?哇!
Huh? Whoa!
哦，天哪!
Oh, geez!
啊!
Aah!
-是你!-爱宝!
-You!-Eyeball!
地球拜拜
There goes the Earth.
我的整个团都拜拜了好吗!
There goes my whole platoon!
简直一团糟!我该怎么写进报告里?!
This is a mess!What'll I say in my report?
我能不能写报告都成问题!
How will I evenmake my report?
简直噩梦!
This is a nightmare!
全都是你的错!
And this is all your fault!
等等，不，才不是!
-Whoa!-Hey, no, it's not!
是你先要伤害我的朋友的!
You were trying to hurt my friends!
但是打开月面基地气阀的人是你!
But you opened the airlock in the moon base!
是你把我们送进了太空--
You sent us flying into space --
还根本没有回家的希望!
with no hope of ever returning!
好吧，也许那个是我的错
Okay, so maybe that was my fault.
对不起-现在高兴了吧?
I'm sorry.There, are you happy?
不高兴
No.
要不是你被泡泡保护着
You're lucky you're in that bubble,
我就一拳打在你脸上
or I'd pop you right in the face.
行啊，你要是一直这么无理取闹
Well, if you're going to be a grump about it,
我们就直接在太空里白头偕老得了!
then we can just float in silence until we both die.
-听起来不错-行!
Sounds great.Fine!
我都等不及去死了!
I can't wait!
我也等不及!
Me, neither!
♪♪
啥?没信号?
What? No signal?
拜托，旁边不就有颗卫星吗?!
Come on,I'm right by a satellite.
如果我没在这里死掉
If I don't die out here,
回地球第一件事就是换个手机套餐
first thing I do back on Earth is change my phone plan.
我就不应该回到这颗蠢星球来!
I shouldn't have ever come back to that dumb planet!
当我听说地球上可能还有水晶战士的时候
When I heard rumors there might still be Crystal Gems on Earth,
我当时都没敢相信
I couldn't believe it.
一千年的战争都徒劳无功!
A thousand years of fighting were all for nothing!
再想想玫瑰石英可能还活着?
And Rose Quartz might still be alive?
她肯定还活着
She must be!
不然为什么铁石英那么重要的人物
Why else would someone as important as Jasper
会回来地球呢?
be back on Earth?
当然是为了确认玫瑰是否活着
For closure, that's why.
我也这么想过
I wanted it, too.
我也想亲眼看看玫瑰石英
I wanted to see Rose Quartz with my own eye.
至少
At the very least,
我以为铁石英会有答案，可...
I thought Jasper might have some answers, but...
那根本不是她--只是另一个把戏
it wasn't even her --just another trick.
这才是你真正想要的?想看看玫瑰石英?
That's what you really wanted?To see Rose Quartz?
比什么都想
More than anything.
那么-今天就是你的幸运日了
Well, then today's your lucky day.
怎么讲?
How's that?
我...
I...
我知道玫瑰石英在哪
know where Rose Quartz is.
啥?她在哪?
What? Where is she?!
她变成了我
She turned into me.
你要是她
Right.
我还有两只眼呢
And I have two eyeballs --
你看看我有吗?
which I don't!
你真的以为我蠢到什么都信，是吧?
You expect me to believe anything, don't you?
耍我一次，我丢人
Fool me once, shame on me.
耍我四次，真的算是耍了我了
Fool me four times,you already fooled me --
我绝不会再上你的当
and you can't fool me again.
你不相信我的话，我可以证明!
Look, I can prove it!
我身上有她的宝石!
I have her Rose Quartz gem!
这宝石看着红中带粉
That's more of a pinkish-red
玫瑰石英的宝石可是粉中带红
than a real Rose Quartz reddish pink.
那是因为你隔着我的泡泡在看啊!
That's because you're looking at it through my bubble!
等下...
Hold on...
来，看这个!
Here, check this out!
看，我能召唤她的盾牌!
Look,I can summon her shield!
你看上面还有玫瑰啥的
It's got a rose on it and everything!
谁管她的盾啊?
Who cares about her shield?
我只记得她有粉色的巨剑
Her huge sword is what I remember.
呃，我把剑丢在狮子那里了
Uh, I left that in my lion...
看
Look.
看看我身上有没有玫瑰的影子
Tell me you don't see the resemblance.
你在逗我?你可真卑鄙
Are you kidding me?You're despicable.
我们都要死在这儿了
We're gonna die out here,
你还要在临死前开我的玩笑
and you're just gonna make fun of me until we do.
你真是比玫瑰石英还残忍
You're even crueler than Rose Quartz.
呃...
Uh...
呃，爱宝?
Uh, Eyeball?
爱宝?!
Eyeball?!
那不是我弄的...
That's not my --
简直不能再棒!
Oh, great!
小行星袭来!
Asteroids incoming!
士兵，各找掩护!
Find cover, soldier!
我已经有掩护了，你倒是找地方躲啊!
I am in cover,you get somewhere safe!
哇!
Wow!
感觉筋骨没年轻时灵活了
I think I'm losing my luster.
我们要撞上那块大的了!
We're heading right for that big one!
不!
No!
哦?
Oh?
哦
Oh.
我还活着
I'm alive.
我们做到啦!
We made it!
我是无敌的!
I'm unstoppable!
爱宝!
Eyeball!
哦，不，不!
Oh, no! No!
我抓到你了
I've got you.
哦天了!你还好吗?
Oh, geez! You okay?
起开!
Get off me!
哇，你怎么了?
Whoa!What's wrong?
哎呀呀!你的宝石开裂了!
Ay-yi-yi!Your gem is cracked!
啥?还能再倒霉点吗?!
What?!This is just perfect!
别担心--我能修复你的宝石!
Don't worry --I can fix your gem!
我才不会信你的鬼---话!
I'm not falling for any of your tricks!
我是认真的--我能帮你
I'm serious -- I can help.
好吧
Fine.
死马当活马医好了
I guess I got nothing else to lose.
谢谢
Thank you.
欸?!
Eh?!
你这是要干啥?!
What was that supposed to be?!
天儿了你脑袋里都在想...
What in the cosmos is wrong with...
什么?
you?
看，成功了!
See? It worked!
我...
I...
我简直不敢相信!
I can't believe it!
过去战场上有个流言--
There were rumors back during the war --
流言说玫瑰石英能够治愈水晶战士们
that Rose Quartz could heal her Crystal Gem soldiers,
把自己的小军队
keeping her small army
打造得能与母星的强大军事力量匹敌
in contention with the superior forces of Homeworld.
哇哦，真的是你!
Wow!It really is you!
玫瑰石英!
Rose Quartz!
现在信了吧?!我一直都在证明这一点!
See?! That's what I was trying to tell ya!
对，就是我--伟大的玫瑰石英!
Yup, it's me --the mighty Rose Quartz!
现在我们被困在这里
And now we're stuck out here,
向宇宙中漫无目的地漂流
floating aimlessly through outer space!
噗
Pff!
我们是怎么把自己搞到这般田地的?
How'd we get ourselves into this mess?
伟大的玫瑰石英
The mighty Rose Quartz.
哈?
Huh?
做梦都想不到我会有这种机会
I never thought I'd get a chance like this.
想不到你会败在我手下!
I can't believe you're all mine!
啥?!
Wah?!
你为啥要攻击我?!
Why are you attacking me?!
别假装惊讶了，玫瑰石英!
Don't act surprised,Rose Quartz!
你碎掉了一颗钻石!
You shattered a Diamond!
哇!
Whoa!
吼吼，我要抓到你啦!
Ooh, I'm gonna get ya!
我要拿到你的宝石带回母星!
I'm gonna take your gem and bring it back!
啥?!不!不要拿走我的宝石!
What?! No!Please don't take my gem!
等下，拿走宝石以后我会怎么样啊?
Wait, what would even happen to me?
-哈?-嗯?
-Huh?!-Hmm?
哈!
Ha!
等-等下!你不必这样做的!
W-Wait!You don't have to do this!
哦，快点认输吧!
Oh, give it up already!
你不会再糟蹋我这次机会了!
You can't take this away from me!
我将会成为一个传说!
I'm gonna be a legend!
我会名留青史!
I'll go down in history!
我红宝石打败玫瑰石英
What will the Diamonds say when they hear
听了这之后钻石她们会怎么想呢?
that a Ruby defeated Rose Quartz?
她们会奖励给我一个专属的珍珠!
They're gonna give me my own pearl!
啥?
Wah?!
等下!听我说!
Wait! Please listen!
我真的不是我妈妈!
I'm really not my mom!
我不想伤害你!
I don't want to hurt you!
你-你要三思啊
Just --Just think for a second.
我们已经迷失在太空了
We're lost out in space.
你打算怎么自己回母星?
How are you going to get back to Homeworld alone?
我已经拿定主意了
I've already made up my mind.
哇
Whoa!
♪ If I could ♪
♪ Begin to be ♪
♪ Half of what you think of me ♪
♪ I could do about anything ♪
♪ I could even learn
how to love ♪
♪ When I see ♪
♪ The way you act ♪
♪ Wondering
when I'm coming back ♪
♪ I could do about anything ♪
♪ I could even learn
how to love ♪
♪ Like you ♪
♪♪
为什么没有人跟我讲过粉钻的事情?
How come nobody told me about Pink Diamond?
战争期间我们做了很多不得已的事
We all did what we had to during the war.
但是现在一切都已经变了
Everything's different now.
但是妈妈真的那么做了吗?
But did mom really do it?
她真的粉碎了粉钻吗?
Did she really shatter her?
她也不得已
She had to.
地球以前是粉钻的
The Earth belonged to Pink Diamond.
摧毁粉钻是拯救地球的唯一出路
Destroying her was the only way to save the planet.
为了紫晶能选择自己命运，为了珍珠能不受束缚
For Amethyst to be herself,for Pearl to be free,
为了我能在一起
for me to be together.
为了你能存在
For you to exist.
但是我以为...
But I thought...
至少她绝对不会...
a-at least she'd never...
她的选择并不只为了她自己的利益
She didn't always do what was best for her.
她做的一切都是为了地球
But she always did what was best for Earth.
甚至不惜粉碎一个宝石
Even if it meant shattering someone.
是的
Yes.
谢谢你们能告诉我
Thanks for telling me.
♪ Love me like you ♪
♪♪